A Guide to the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation Correspondence and Subject files, 1970-2022
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Director of the Virginia Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation Correspond and Subject files, 1970-2022
The Library of Virginia
34743, 34883, 35466, 39056, 41519, 42374, 42722, 44932, 45393, 51229
50 cu. ft. (50 boxes)
Virginia. Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation. Office of the Director.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years. It may be necessary for an archivist to review any unprocessed, modern record collections (those collections less than 75 years old) that may contain confidential information before the records can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of records can be made for patrons. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for more details before planning your research trip.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 17 October 1994 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 34743].
Transferred on 11 May 1995 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 34883].
Transferred on 1 August 1997 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 35466].
Transferred on 15 January 2002 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 39056].
Transferred on 20 October 2004 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 41519].
Transferred on 21 December 2005 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 42374].
Transferred on 19 June 2006 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 3600 W. Broad. St., Richmond, VA 23230 [Acc. 42722].
Transferred on 15 April 2010 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 9960 Mayland Dr., Suite 400, Richmond, VA 23233 [Acc. 44932].
Transferred on 8 February 2011 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 9960 Mayland Dr., Suite 400, Richmond, VA 23233 [Acc. 45393].
Transferred on 4 February 2014 by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 9960 Mayland Dr., Suite 400, Richmond, VA 23233 [Acc. 51229].
Biographical Information
The Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation was formed in 1948 under the Government Reorganization Act. On March 24, 1978, the agency's name was changed to the Dept. of Commerce. Effective July, 1993, the Department regained its original name. Currently, the Department is responsible for the these Boards: Appraisers (real estate), Architects, Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, Auctioneers, Barbers, Body Piercing, Branch Pilots, Cemetery, Common Interest Community, Contractors, Cosmetology, Fair Housing, Geology, Hearing Aid Specialists, Interior Designers, Land Surveyors, Landscape Architects, Opticians, Polygraph Examiners, Professional Boxing and Wrestling, Professional Engineers, Professional Soil Scientists and Wetland Professionals, Real estate brokers, Surveyor Photogrammetrist, Tattooing, Tradesmen Licensure, Waste Management Facility Operators, and Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals.
The primary function of the Department is to provide administrative support to the boards within the Department which are currently responsible for licensing and certification of occupations. The Boards have regulatory authority for the issuance, suspension and revocation of certificates, permits, and licenses. The Department is operated by a director who is appointed by the Governor. The Department's activities are broken-down into sub-programs for each of the examining boards. Major activities include review and evaluation of the regulation of professions, examination of those wishing to enter one of the regulated professions, licensing, consumer complaint resolution, and investigation of alleged violations or laws. The mission of the Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation is to protect the health, safety and welfare of Virginians, while promoting a competent workforce, fair housing opportunities, and a productive economy.
Scope and Content
Records
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 34743]
Series II: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 34883]
Series III: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 35466]
Series IV: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 39056]
Series V: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 41519]
Series VI: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 42374]
Series VII: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 42722]
Series VIII: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 44932]
Series IX: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 45393]
Series X: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 51229].
Contents List
- Series I: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 34743],., Extent: 50 cu. ft. (50 boxes). (Box 1-)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Public hearings, 1985 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Hearings and Regulations, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Regulatory Review, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Regulatory Reform 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Proposed amendments to rules and regulations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Regulatory Reform and Review, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Hearings and Regulations, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Regulatory Review, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - State Board of Architects, Professional Engineers, Landscape Surveyors, and Certified Landscape Architects (APELSCLA), Regulatory Review, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - APELSCLA, Notice of hearing, 1981 March (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - APELSCLA, Regulatory Review, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - APELSCLA, Proposed Regulations, 1985 March (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - APELSCLA, Regulatory Review, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - APELSCLA, Regulatory Review, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - APELSCLA, Regulatory Review, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - State Board for Contractors, Regulatory Review, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State Board for Contractors, Regulations, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - State Board for Contractors, Proposed Regulations, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - State Board for Contractors, Final Regulations, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - State Board for Contractors, Regulations, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - State Board for Contractors, Contractor Examination, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - State Board for Contractors, Proposed Regulations, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - State Board for Contractors, Final Regulations, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - State Board for Contractors, Public comments for Proposed legislation, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - State Board for Contractors, Regulations, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Agency service agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Agency service agreement, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Biennial report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Board members training, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Directives and policies, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Conflict of Interest Act, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Complaint handling, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Efficiency in government, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Financial disclosure, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Grievance panel, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Grievance panel, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Hermitage Enterprises contract, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Literary Fund deposits, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dept. of Commerce, IBM, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Management Information Systems plan, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Management study, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Management study, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Performance handbook for supervisors, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Commerce, P-14 expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Operations, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Transparencies, ca. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Minority management intern program, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Recovery fund task force, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Dept. of Commerce, RFP, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dept. of Commerce, The Virginia Register, Form, Style, and Procedure manual, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Memorandum, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
  - Attorney General, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1987 Nov. 23 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 July 25 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 Aug. 10 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 Aug. 29 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 June 20 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 July 6 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 Apr. 25 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 Mar. 21 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1988 Feb. 22 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1987 Jan. 11 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board meetings, 1987 Oct. 26 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Merger with Barber and Cosmetology in other states, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Complaint tracking enforcement, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Monthly financial statements, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Regulatory Review, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Annual conference, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Task Force on speciality license (skin care), 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Board of Cosmetology, National Interstate Council of State Boards of Cosmetology, Inc., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Memorandum, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Board agendas, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Associations, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Minutes, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Fee verification, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Board of Real Estate, Proposed legislation, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3-6)
  - Board of Real Estate, Proposed legislation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7-10)
  - Board of Real Estate, General Assembly and legislation, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Board of Real Estate, Termination files, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  - Board of Real Estate, Meetings and minutes, 1976-1990 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - APELSCLA, Proposed bill, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Board of Commerce, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Board of Commerce, Survey of collegial bodies, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Board of Commerce, Electrolysis licensure study, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Board of Commerce, Meetings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Board of Commerce, Licensing certification study, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Board of Commerce, Geologists Board, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Board of Commerce, Gold and silver dealers, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Board of Commerce, Home improvement contractors study, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Board of Commerce, Property management report, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Board of Commerce, Virginia Real Estate Commission manual and regulations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Board of Commerce, Property management study, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
  - Board of Commerce, Educational Clerical employees certification, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Board of Commerce, Report on need for regulation of flea market operations, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Board of Commerce, Property management public meeting, 1980 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Board of Commerce, Power engineer study, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Board member orientation, 1985 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bernard L. Henderson, Jr. (Director), Memorandum, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Public hearing comments, 1983 Nov. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Thomas A. Dick (Policy analyst), Memorandum (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - APELSCLA, Proposed regulation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Regulatory review, Training session, 1983 March (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Regulatory review, Task Force meeting notes, 1983 March-June (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Regulatory review, Workplan, 1973 Feb. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Regulatory review, Indexes and recommendations, 1984 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Regulatory review, Blank forms, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Regulatory review, Training session overheads, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Regulatory review, Reform Advisory Board meeting, 1983 May (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Regulatory review, Workplans, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Regulatory review, Meeting, 1983 May (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Regulatory review, Workplans, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Regulatory review, Dept. Commerce self audit, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Regulatory review, Workplans, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - National Cosmetology Test, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Nursing Home Administrator, Survey analysis, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Private Security Services, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Fire sprinkler designs, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Regulation of Tax preparers, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Study of Auctioneers, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - State Board of Accountancy, Review, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Board of Commerce, Staff report, 1984 May (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Regulations, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - State Board of Examiners of Professional Hairdressers, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with General Assembly members (alphabetically by last name) (Box 10)
  - Assistant Attorney General, Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Law Enforcement, Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Finance, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Data systems, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fair housing, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Property registration, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Powhatan Plantation, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Office, Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Real Estate Board vs. Merrill W. Gitlin, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Newsletters (Notes), 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Meetings, 1990 July 30 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Meetings, 1990 June 18 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Meetings, 1990 Nov. 26 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Meetings, 1990 Aug. 27 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Board of Cosmetology, Meetings, 1990 Oct. 15 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate Board Case Reviews, Meetings, 1990 Aug. 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Board Case Reviews, Meetings, 1990 Sept.-Oct. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Board Case Reviews, Meetings, 1990 Dec. 19 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Board, Correspondence, 1987 October (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Board, Correspondence, 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Board, Meetings, 1987 Nov. 23 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Board, Correspondence, 1987 December (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Agency agreement plans, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Agency agreement plans, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - List of designated officials to the General Assembly (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - List of designated officials to the General Assembly, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - List of designated officials to the General Assembly, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Financial disclosure forms, Board members, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Anti-trust reports, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Operational procedures, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Conflict of Interests Act, 1970-1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Conflict of Interests Act, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Correspondence, David R. Hathcock, Director, 1988 July (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Correspondence, David R. Hathcock, Director, 1988 August (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Correspondence, David R. Hathcock, Director, 1988 September (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Correspondence, David R. Hathcock, Director, 1988 October (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Correspondence, David R. Hathcock, Director, 1988 November (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Correspondence, David R. Hathcock, Director, 1988 December (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Real Estate Commission, Survey, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Memorandum, 1988 May-1989 May (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Senior Deputy Director weekly reports, 1988 July-1989 June (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Administrator weekly reports, 1988 July-1989 June (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - APELSLA, Board members, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Asbestos Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Contractors complaints, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Contractor Transaction Recovvery Fund, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Contractors Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Personnel, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Revised wage employment policy, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Pilots Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Policy Analyst, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Polygraph Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Private Security Services, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Property registration administration, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Real Estate Transaction Recovery Fund, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Regulatory Review Committee, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Cosmetology Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Data systems, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Enforcement Division, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Fair Housing, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Budget and Finance, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Geology Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Real Estate Board, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Licensing Division, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Examination Division, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Licensing and Examinations, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Opticians Board, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Legislative proposals, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Division of Legislative Services, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Sr. Deputy Director, Ronald K. Layne, Correspondence, 1988 July-1989 July (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Misc., 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director David R. Hathcock, Memorandum, 1984-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Sr. Deputy Director Ronald K. Layne, Memorandum, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Fair Housing Administration, Memorandum, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Sr. Deputy Director Ronald K. Layne, Weekly reports, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Board, Weekly reports, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Administrator, Weekly reports, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Accountancy Board, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Accountancy lawsuit, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Non-certified accountants, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - APELSCLA Board, Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Asbestos, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Asbestos, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Asbestos Board, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Board, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Auctioneers Board, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Barbers Board, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Contractors Board, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cosmetology Board, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Data analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Law enforcement, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Law enforcement, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Real Estate Board, Meetings, 1990 March (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Board, Meetings, 1990 May (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Board, Meetings, 1990 June (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Board, Time-Share Regulations Advisory Committee, Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
  - Real Estate Board, Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate Board, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3-6)
  - Real Estate Board, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7-12)
  - Regulations, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Time Share Advisory Meeting, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Personnel, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Cole vs. Guffey, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Ronald K. Layne, Presentation, 1986 June (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Reports on Audit, 1982, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Memorandum, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Dept. of Information Technology, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Assistant Attorney General, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Finance, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
  - Dept. of Finance, Corrective Action Plan Audit, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Sec. of Economic Development, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1987 January-May (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1987 May-September (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1987 August-October (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1987 October-December (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Real Estate Board Meetings, 1989 January 13 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Board Meetings, 1989 March 22 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Board Meetings, 1989 May 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate, Condominium and Timeshare Regulations, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate, Condominium and Timeshare Regulations, Public comments and meetings, 1987 January (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
  - Fair Housing, 1982-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fair Housing, 1985-1986 June (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fair Housing, 1986 June-October (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fair Housing, 1986 December-1987 May (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Nursing Home Administrators, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fair Housing Workplan (draft), 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fair Housing, Tri State Consortium, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Polygraph proposed regulations, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)